Finding Aid for Penrod/Hiawatha Company postcard collection, 1950-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Penrod / Hiawatha Postcards 2001-2004
  - Lakes, Lighthouses, Parks, etc.
    - Lighthouses
      - Grand Island North Light (Box 8)
      - Grand Traverse (Box 8)
      - Gull Rock (Box 8)
      - Holland Harbor (Box 8)
      - Little Sable Point (Box 8)
      - Little Traverse (Box 8)
      - Ludington (Box 8)
      - Manistee (Box 8)
      - Marquette Harbor (Box 8)
      - Menominee North Pier (Box 8)
      - North Pier (Box 8)
      - Old Grand Island (Box 8)
      - Old Mackinac Point (Box 8)
      - Old Mission Point (Box 8)
      - Old Presque Isle (Box 8)
      - Point Betsie (Box 8)
      - Point Iroquois (Box 8)
      - Pointe aux Barques (Box 8)
      - Presque Isle (Box 8)
      - Round Island (Box 8)
      - Sand Hills (Box 8)
      - Sand Point (Box 8)
      - Seul Choix (Box 8)
      - South Haven (Box 8)
      - South Manitou (Box 8)
      - Spectacle Reef (Box 8)
      - St. Joseph North Pier (Box 8)
      - Sturgeon Point (Box 8)
      - Tawas Point (Box 8)
      - White River (Box 8)
      - White Shoal (Box 8)
      - Whitefish Point (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
    - Parks
      - Fayette State Historic (Box 8)
      - Fort Wilkins (Box 8)
      - Hartwick Pines State (Box 8)
      - Higgins (Box 8)
      - Huron-Manistee National Forest (Box 8)
      - Keweenaw National Historic (Box 8)
      - Palms Book State (Box 8)
      - Pictured Rocks/Cruises (Box 8)
      - Porcupine (Box 8)
      - Quincy Mine Hoist (Box 8)
      - Silver Lake (Box 8)
      - Sleeping Bean National Park (Box 8)
      - Warren Dunes (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
    - Regions
      - Au Sable Rivermouth (Box 8)
      - Copper Country (Box 8)
      - Drummond Island (Box 8)
      - Inland Waterway (Box 8)
      - Les Cheneaux Islands (Box 8)
      - Soo Locks (Box 8)
      - St. Joseph River (Box 8)
      - Tahquamenon Region (Box 8)
      - Thumb Area (Box 8)
      - Traverse Bay (Box 8)
      - Upper Peninsula (Box 8)
      - Waterfalls (Box 8)
- Penrod / Hiawatha Postcards 2005-2014
  The Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards 2005-2014 series contain postcards produced approximately 2005-2014. The series is primarily arranged first by general postcards of non-specific Michigan locations and topics. This is followed by the listing by city, then such tourist destinations as lighthouses, parks, rivers, etc.
  - General
    - Amish (Box 9)
    - Animals (Box 9)
    - Attractions / Museums (Box 9)
    - Bridges, Tridges
      - Blue Water Bridge (Box 9)
      - Mackinac Bridge (Box 9)
      - Midland Tridge (Box 9)
      - Stewart J. Cort & International Bridge (Box 9)
      - Whites Covered Bridge (Box 9)
    - Churches (Box 9)
    - Humor (Box 9)
    - Seasons (Box 9)
    - Ships & Ferries (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
  - Cities
    - Algonac (Box 9)
    - Battle Creek (Box 9)
    - Bay City (Box 9)
    - Berrien Springs (Box 9)
    - Beulah-Benzonia (Box 9)
    - Cadillac (Box 9)
    - Calumet (Box 9)
    - Charlevoix (Box 9)
    - Copper Harbor (Box 9)
    - Detroit (Box 9)
    - Dickinson County (Box 9)
    - Elk Rapids (Box 9)
    - Escanaba (Box 9)
    - Fayette (Box 9)
    - Frankenmuth (Box 9)
    - Frankfort (Box 9)
    - Gaylord (Box 9)
    - Gladstone (Box 9)
    - Grand Haven (Box 9)
    - Grand Marais (Box 9)
    - Grand Rapids (Box 9)
    - Harbor Springs (Box 9)
    - Holland (Hope College) (Box 9)
    - Houghton / Hancock (Box 9)
    - Iron Mountain (Box 9)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 9)
    - Lansing (Michigan State University) (Box 9)
    - Leland (Box 9)
    - Ludington (Box 9)
    - Mackinac Bridge (Box 9)
    - Mackinac Island (Box 9)
    - Mackinaw City (Box 9)
    - Manistee (Box 9)
    - Manistique (Box 9)
    - Marquette (Northern Michigan University) (Box 9)
    - Midland (Box 9)
    - Muskegon (Box 9)
    - New Buffalo (Box 9)
    - Pentwater (Box 9)
    - Petoskey (Box 9)
    - Port Huron (Box 9)
    - Saugatuck (Box 9)
    - Sault Ste. Marie (Box 9)
    - South Haven (Box 9)
    - South Manitou Island (Box 9)
    - St. Clair (Box 9)
    - St. Ignace (Box 9)
    - St. Joseph (Box 9)
    - Suttons Bay (Box 9)
    - Tawas Bay (Box 9)
    - Traverse City (Box 9)
  - Lakes, Rivers & Springs
    - Escanaba River (Box 9)
    - Great Lakes (Box 9)
    - Gun Lake (Box 9)
    - Higgins Lake (Box 9)
    - Houghton Lake (Box 9)
    - Kitch-iti-kipi, The Big Spring (Box 9)
    - Lake Antoine (Box 9)
    - Lake Huron (Box 9)
    - Lake of the Clouds (Box 9)
    - Lake Superior (Box 9)
    - Lake Michigan (Box 9)
    - Manistee River (Box 9)
    - Torch Lake (Box 9)
  - Lighthouses
    - Big Sable Point (Box 9)
    - Charlevoix South Pier Light (Box 9)
    - Cheboygan (Box 9)
    - Copper Harbor (Box 9)
    - Crisp Point (Box 9)
    - Eagle Harbor (Box 9)
    - Fort Gratiot (Box 9)
    - Forty Mile Point (Box 9)
    - Frankfort (Box 9)
    - Grand Island East Channel (Box 9)
    - Grand Traverse (Box 9)
    - Great Lakes (Box 9)
    - Holland Harbor (Box 9)
    - Keweenaw Lights (Box 9)
    - Lake Erie Lighthouses (Box 9)
    - Lake Huron Lighthouses (Box 9)
    - Lake Superior Lighthouses (Box 9)
    - Little Sable Point (Box 9)
    - Little Traverse Lighthouse (Box 9)
    - Ludington (Box 9)
    - Mackinac Island (Box 9)
    - Manistee (Box 9)
    - Manistique (Box 9)
    - Manning Memorial (Box 9)
    - Marine City (Box 9)
    - Marquette Harbor (Box 9)
    - McGulpin Point (Box 9)
    - Mendota (Bete Grise) (Box 9)
    - Menominee North Pier (Box 9)
    - Michigan Lighthouses (Box 9)
    - Mission Point (Box 9)
    - North Pier (Box 9)
    - Old Mackinac Point (Box 9)
    - Old Mission Peninsula (Box 9)
    - Old Mission Point (Box 9)
    - Old Presque Isle (Box 9)
    - Peninsula Point (Box 9)
    - Point Betsie (Box 9)
    - Point Iroquois (Box 9)
    - Pointe Aux Barques (Box 9)
    - Port Sanilac (Box 9)
    - Round Island (Box 9)
    - Sand Point (Box 9)
    - Seul Choix (Box 9)
    - South Haven (Box 9)
    - South Manitou Island (Box 9)
    - St. Joseph (Box 9)
    - Sturgeon Point (Box 9)
    - Tawas Point (Box 9)
    - West Michigan (Box 9)
    - White River (Box 9)
    - White Shoal (Box 9)
    - Whitefish Point (Box 9)
  - Parks
    - Bayfront (Box 9)
    - Brockway Mountain Drive (Box 9)
    - Fort Wilkins Historic State (Box 9)
    - Grand Haven State (Box 9)
    - Holland Harbor State (Box 9)
    - Ludington State (Box 9)
    - Ludington Waterfront (Box 9)
    - Pictured Rocks/Cruises (Box 9)
    - Quincy Mine Hoist (Box 9)
    - Silver Lake (Box 9)
    - Sleeping Bear National Park (Box 9)
  - Regions
    - Au Sable Rivermouth (Box 9)
    - Copper Country (Box 9)
    - Drummond Island (Box 9)
    - Soo Locks (Box 9)
    - Tahquamenon Region (Box 9)
    - Traverse Bay (Box 9)
    - Upper Peninsula (Box 9)
    - Waterfalls (Box 9)
- Oversize and miscellaneous
  This series includes a photocopy of a two-page newspaper article containing biographical information about John Penrod and the Penrod/Hiawatha Postcard Company (Ann Arbor News, July 7, 1991). In addition, there are larger than average postcards, foldout souvenir postcard packets, and roadmaps used by Penrod in providing a geographic code to each postcard.
  - Clippings relating John Penrod and his company 1991 (Box 10)
  - Oversize postcards
    - Lighthouses (Box 10)
    - Cities and parks (Box 10)
    - State and general (Box 10)
  - Foldout souvenir postcard packets (Box 10)
    (include Christmas themed packet)
  - State road maps used by Penrod in coding his postcards (Box 10)